<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything We Know About &#39;Saand Ki Aankh&#39; Starring Taapsee &amp; Bhumi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/upcoming-movie-saand-ki-aankh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/upcoming-movie-saand-ki-aankh/</guid>
      <description>Anurag Kashyap is back with yet another offbeat film called Saand Ki Aankh starring Taapsee Pannu and Bhumi Pednekar. These badass women are going to play two real-life badass 60-somethings who happen to be sharpshooters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why You Must Follow Sushmita Sen on Instagram</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/5-reasons-follow-sushmita-sen-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/5-reasons-follow-sushmita-sen-instagram/</guid>
      <description>Sushmita Sen keeps it real and relatable. Scrolling through her anecdotes, fitness videos and posts about her daughters, all we feel is positivity!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities who spoke about their anxiety and depression</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/bollywood-celebs-spoke-about-anxiety-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/bollywood-celebs-spoke-about-anxiety-depression/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot to open up about it, that too on a public platform. But these heroes stepped up just for the sake of normalising these issues so that people can take heed and understand it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Ranbir Kapoor Movies of All Time</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/top-5-ranbir-kapoor-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/top-5-ranbir-kapoor-movies/</guid>
      <description>Ranbir Kapoor has time and again proven his acting proficiency and given us a number of blockbuster hits in the last 10 years of his shining career. We list a few that won our hearts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apt Bollywood Songs for Top GoT Scenes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/apt-songs-bollywood-game-of-thrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/apt-songs-bollywood-game-of-thrones/</guid>
      <description>The heady mix of dragons and nudity does work wonders for TRP. But what connects it to our old school Bollywood is perhaps the element of drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalank</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/kalank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/kalank/</guid>
      <description>The lives of six enigmatic characters become entangled whilst in search of love, but separated by the dichotomy between the two worlds of Husnabad, a town in North India.
Kalank | World of Kalank Kalank is a movie that is high on glitz, glamour, and grandeur. So to create the World of Kalank, the best minds in Bollywood came together to create something timeless. From the miniatures and sets to the lights and the costumes, here’s how it all came to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: Rajkummar Rao</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-rajkumar-rao/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-rajkumar-rao/</guid>
      <description>Rajkummar Rao is a chameleon. He can be an introvert as Govind in Kai Po Che and a flamboyant Pritam in Bareilly Ki Barfi. There ain’t no role this perfectionist can’t pull off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Unconventional Leading Actors Of Bollywood Today</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/unconventional-actors-bollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/unconventional-actors-bollywood/</guid>
      <description>These Unconventional actors have successfully proved that it’s not all about the songs, the dance or the good looks; but - the art of acting and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsoons bring out the Bollywood in everyone!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/monsoons-bring-out-the-bollywood-in-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/monsoons-bring-out-the-bollywood-in-everyone/</guid>
      <description>The peculiar smell of first rains of monsoon often makes me reminisce about the era of Raj Kapoor &amp;amp; Nargis romancing under their umbrella while singing pyaar hua ikraar hua!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raees</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/raees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/raees/</guid>
      <description>Raees is running an illegal liquor business in Gujarat. His life and business and doing great until ACP Majmudar is posted in his area. ACP Majmudar is hell bent on stopping all the illegal trading activities of Raees. Now Raees must fight to save his business and himself too. Watch behind the scenes videos of Raees to see all the fun and hard work done in the making of this movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things That Happen When You Meet A Celebrity</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/when-you-meet-a-celebrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/when-you-meet-a-celebrity/</guid>
      <description>Funny things happen when you meet a celebrity. I speak from experience. Living in Mumbai has its perks, and I’ve found myself exactly where these B-town biggies were a few lucky times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Life Is A Movie: How Bollywood Defines Most Indians</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/how-indian-cinema-defines-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/how-indian-cinema-defines-lives/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I have observed how Indian Cinema has created a universe of its own, an aspirational bubble that every Indian craves to be a part of!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: Taapsee Pannu</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-taapsee-pannu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-taapsee-pannu/</guid>
      <description>The loud-heart, the feisty and the ever-empowered Taapsee Pannu has won our hearts with her fierce roles and fearless persona.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly LLB 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/jolly-llb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/jolly-llb-2/</guid>
      <description>Jolly is a clumsy lawyer who is faced with representing the most critical court case of his career.
Jolly LLB 2 | A Jolly Good Cast | Akshay Kumar | Huma Qureshi Meet the extremely talented Jolly Good Cast members and know something more about the film and the characters. These facts are something you cannot miss about Jolly LL.B 2.
  Jolly LLB 2 | Jolly - The New Birbal | Akshay Kumar He is goofy, he is street smart, he is extremely intelligent and he is the most lovable character!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Romantic Dramas to Fresh New Genres, How Bollywood has evolved</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/how-bollywood-has-evolved/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/how-bollywood-has-evolved/</guid>
      <description>We’re not saying Bollywood didn’t have any other genre, we sure did. But somehow the base theme of action, comedy, thriller, or even sci-fi film was always a mushy love story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender Pay Gap in Bollywood &amp; Why Deepika Padukone Called It Out</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/gender-pay-gap-bollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/gender-pay-gap-bollywood/</guid>
      <description>How do we feel about the same industry when they go about with the age-old and unfair practice of the gender pay gap! Well, times have changed and the Bollywood woman of today like to speak their heart out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ittefaq</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/ittefaq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/ittefaq/</guid>
      <description>Vikram is an acclaimed British author who has come to India for a book launch. But when his wife is found dead in their hotel room he is the prime suspect in the murder. What’s more is that he is also the prime suspect in a total stranger’s murder. Now Dev, the dashing police investigator must find out the truth behind the double murders.
Sidharth Malhotra as Vikram | Making of Ittefaq   Akshaye Khanna as Dev | Making of Ittefaq   Sonakshi Sinha as Maya | Making of Ittefaq   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: Kangana Ranaut</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-kangana-ranaut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-kangana-ranaut/</guid>
      <description>Call her Queen, Datto, Simran or Manikarnika, the feisty and daring Kangana Ranaut has created her own glorious niche in Bollywood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Has Bollywood grown out of &#39;happy endings&#39;?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/bollywood-has-no-happy-endings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/bollywood-has-no-happy-endings/</guid>
      <description>We’re talking about Bollywood going beyond the idea of happy endings. They’re starting to experiment with open-endings and looming curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: Kalki Koechlin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-kalki-koechlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/spotlight-kalki-koechlin/</guid>
      <description>Kalki has time and again proven to be the epitome of experimentation. Her characters can whisper as softly and bawl as loudly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badrinath ki Dulhania</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/badrinath-ki-dulhania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/badrinath-ki-dulhania/</guid>
      <description>Badrinath Bansal from Jhansi and Vaidehi Trivedi from Kota belong to small towns but have diametrically opposite opinions on everything. This leads to a clash of ideologies, despite both of them recognizing the goodness in each other.
The making of Badri and his Dulhania - Badrinath Ki Dulhania | Varun Dhawan | Alia Bhatt When all heart &amp;amp; the fiery come together, you get Badri &amp;amp; Vaidehi. Watch Varun Dhawan &amp;amp; Alia Bhatt unplugged, talking about Badri &amp;amp; his Dulhania&amp;rsquo;s quirks, similarities and differences from their real selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Choose Sara Ali Khan Over Janhvi Kapoor. Here’s Why.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/sara-ali-khan-janhvi-kapoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/sara-ali-khan-janhvi-kapoor/</guid>
      <description>Although there is nothing beyond healthy competition between the two, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but pit them against each other on the basis of their debut films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Ode to Retro Star Shammi Kapoor</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/an-ode-to-retro-star-shammi-kapoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/an-ode-to-retro-star-shammi-kapoor/</guid>
      <description>Shammi Kapoor&amp;rsquo;s movies had the most foot-tapping music and his iconic Elvis Presley inspired hair plus dance moves took the 60s party vibe to an all new level. He basically taught India how to party back in the day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being A Badass Villain: Boon or Curse in Bollywood?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/badass-villain-bollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/badass-villain-bollywood/</guid>
      <description>No doubt these nasty Villains give us the creeps! But If you give it a thought, the iconic villain-dialogues are more famous than the heroic ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Character artists in Bollywood</title>
      <link>http://example.org/featured/character-artist-bollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/featured/character-artist-bollywood/</guid>
      <description>Call them subordinates, sidekicks or supporting actors, movies are incomplete without their dynamic acts and we’re here to give their journey a big shoutout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Gentleman</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/a-gentleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/a-gentleman/</guid>
      <description>A gentleman is a story about Gaurav who is on a mission to settle down. He is in the process of trying to charm Kavya into creating life with him and getting married. However, Kavya dreads the thought of taking the plunge and settling down. Her only wish is that her “sundar susheel” gentleman lives life to the full, with a little more risk and excitement. However, things take an interesting twist when an assignment takes Gaurav to Mumbai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our obsession for Celebrity Weddings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/opinion/obsession-with-celebrity-weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/opinion/obsession-with-celebrity-weddings/</guid>
      <description>What we find hilarious and borderline crazy, is the obsessive reaction that follows a celebrity wedding, and ‘viral’ doesn’t even begin to describe the maniacal internet frenzy about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://example.org/search/index.json</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 15:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/search/index.json</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>