<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Behind The Scenes on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Behind The Scenes on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 04:28:21 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalank</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/kalank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/kalank/</guid>
      <description>The lives of six enigmatic characters become entangled whilst in search of love, but separated by the dichotomy between the two worlds of Husnabad, a town in North India.
Kalank | World of Kalank Kalank is a movie that is high on glitz, glamour, and grandeur. So to create the World of Kalank, the best minds in Bollywood came together to create something timeless. From the miniatures and sets to the lights and the costumes, here’s how it all came to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raees</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/raees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/raees/</guid>
      <description>Raees is running an illegal liquor business in Gujarat. His life and business and doing great until ACP Majmudar is posted in his area. ACP Majmudar is hell bent on stopping all the illegal trading activities of Raees. Now Raees must fight to save his business and himself too. Watch behind the scenes videos of Raees to see all the fun and hard work done in the making of this movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly LLB 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/jolly-llb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/jolly-llb-2/</guid>
      <description>Jolly is a clumsy lawyer who is faced with representing the most critical court case of his career.
Jolly LLB 2 | A Jolly Good Cast | Akshay Kumar | Huma Qureshi Meet the extremely talented Jolly Good Cast members and know something more about the film and the characters. These facts are something you cannot miss about Jolly LL.B 2.
  Jolly LLB 2 | Jolly - The New Birbal | Akshay Kumar He is goofy, he is street smart, he is extremely intelligent and he is the most lovable character!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ittefaq</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/ittefaq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/ittefaq/</guid>
      <description>Vikram is an acclaimed British author who has come to India for a book launch. But when his wife is found dead in their hotel room he is the prime suspect in the murder. What’s more is that he is also the prime suspect in a total stranger’s murder. Now Dev, the dashing police investigator must find out the truth behind the double murders.
Sidharth Malhotra as Vikram | Making of Ittefaq   Akshaye Khanna as Dev | Making of Ittefaq   Sonakshi Sinha as Maya | Making of Ittefaq   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badrinath ki Dulhania</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/badrinath-ki-dulhania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/badrinath-ki-dulhania/</guid>
      <description>Badrinath Bansal from Jhansi and Vaidehi Trivedi from Kota belong to small towns but have diametrically opposite opinions on everything. This leads to a clash of ideologies, despite both of them recognizing the goodness in each other.
The making of Badri and his Dulhania - Badrinath Ki Dulhania | Varun Dhawan | Alia Bhatt When all heart &amp;amp; the fiery come together, you get Badri &amp;amp; Vaidehi. Watch Varun Dhawan &amp;amp; Alia Bhatt unplugged, talking about Badri &amp;amp; his Dulhania&amp;rsquo;s quirks, similarities and differences from their real selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Gentleman</title>
      <link>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/a-gentleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/behind-the-scenes/a-gentleman/</guid>
      <description>A gentleman is a story about Gaurav who is on a mission to settle down. He is in the process of trying to charm Kavya into creating life with him and getting married. However, Kavya dreads the thought of taking the plunge and settling down. Her only wish is that her “sundar susheel” gentleman lives life to the full, with a little more risk and excitement. However, things take an interesting twist when an assignment takes Gaurav to Mumbai.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>